<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aviator on Sławomir Liszniański</title>
    <link>/blog/aviator/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aviator on Sławomir Liszniański</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Slawomir Lisznianski &amp;#60;sl@aggati.com&amp;#62;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 01:13:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/aviator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IMC in London, KY</title>
      <link>/blog/aviator/2021-03-15-london-kentucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aviator/2021-03-15-london-kentucky/</guid>
      <description>On March 12th, we flew to Kentucky. Originally, we planned to fly to Knoxville, Tennessee however IMC conditions prevented safe flight to our intended destination. We landed earlier - at KLOZ - and stayed overnight in London, KY. Curtesy of AllTrails, we found an amazing hike to &amp;ldquo;Pine Island Double Falls&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurah! I passed the IFR written test</title>
      <link>/blog/aviator/2021-02-19-ifr-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aviator/2021-02-19-ifr-exam/</guid>
      <description>On my road to IFR cert:
 log 50 hours of cross-country flight time 40 hours of actual or simulated instrument time, of which 15 must be with a CFII  3 hours in an appropriate airplane and within two calendar months of the checkride an IFR cross-country with an instructor (250NM, an approach at each airport and 3 kinds of approaches)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking old friend for his first flight in Cessna</title>
      <link>/blog/aviator/2021-02-02-kdpa-rajesh-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aviator/2021-02-02-kdpa-rajesh-first/</guid>
      <description>My friendship with Rajesh dates back to early 2000. We met at The Options Clearing Corp in Chicago where we both worked as C++ programmers. We&amp;rsquo;ve always had a lot of fun and hang out together to this day.
Other than complaining about the low cabin temperature, Rajesh took it great.
In April of 2011, along with 4 awesome people, we took a bike trip through California and Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New home: DuPage Airport (KDPA)</title>
      <link>/blog/aviator/2021-01-20-kdpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aviator/2021-01-20-kdpa/</guid>
      <description>Last week I joined the &amp;ldquo;International Flying Club&amp;rdquo; out of DuPage, Illinois. Check them out!
My first flight of the week had me tackle 30kts gusts. The wind was strong enough to tilt the camera shortly after take-off, as seen on the video.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RV-10 build log</title>
      <link>/blog/aviator/2021-01-09-rv10-buildlog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 23:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aviator/2021-01-09-rv10-buildlog/</guid>
      <description>Jan &amp;lsquo;21 - Arrival of parts Truck with parts from Vans and Lycoming Unpacking and inventory checking </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinning with GPS overlay</title>
      <link>/blog/aviator/2020-05-04-karr-spin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aviator/2020-05-04-karr-spin/</guid>
      <description>As part of my spin-recovery training, I had a chance to fly this beautiful Decathlon.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
